[
    {"question": "pgeonhole sb/sth", "answer": "〜を決め付ける"},
    {"question": "peace of mind", "answer": "安心感"},
    {"question": "that's the way the cookie crumbles", "answer": "人生そんなもん"},
    {"question": "open (up) Pandora's box", "answer": "問題を引き起こす"},
    {"question": "music to my ears", "answer": "最高の知らせ、嬉しい知らせ"},
    {"question": "showboat", "answer": "ナメたプレーをする"},
    {"question": "take shape", "answer": "具体的になる"},
    {"question": "get to the heart of the matter", "answer": "問題の核心を突く"},
    {"question": "cut sth in many different ways", "answer": "〜を色々な角度でとらえる"},
    {"question": "piture-perfect", "answer": "（絵に描いたように）完璧な、理想的な"},
    {"question": "make sb's blood boil", "answer": "〜を激怒させる、イライラさせる"},
    {"question": "roll off the tongue", "answer": "言いやすい、発音しやすい"},
    {"question": "no hard feelings", "answer": "恨みっこなし、怒りなし"},
    {"question": "kick sb when sb is down", "answer": "〜に追い打ちをかける"},
    {"question": "soldier on", "answer": "負けずに頑張る"},
    {"question": "take away from sth", "answer": "〜の価値を下げる"},
    {"question": "bet one's house on sth/(that)", "answer": "確実に〜する"},
    {"question": "every man and his dog", "answer": "ものすごい数の人"},
    {"question": "play second fiddle to sb/sth", "answer": "（地位や立場が）〜よりも下にいる"},
    {"question": "play with house money", "answer": "何があっても損することはない"},

    {"question": "fact of life", "answer": "紛れもない現実、人生の現実"},
    {"question": "a dime a dozen", "answer": "ゴロゴロいる"},
    {"question": "elephant in the room", "answer": "誰も触れたくない話題"},
    {"question": "few and far between", "answer": "めずらしい、滅多にない"},
    {"question": "with a straight face", "answer": "真顔で"},
    {"question": "go off the rails", "answer": "おかしくなる"},
    {"question": "once in a blue moon", "answer": "めったにない"},
    {"question": "so far so good", "answer": "今のところ、良い感じ"},
    {"question": "at a loss for words", "answer": "絶句した、言葉が見つからない"},
    {"question": "safety net", "answer": "万が一の保険"},
    {"question": "sink or swim", "answer": "死ぬか生きるか"},
    {"question": "get cold feet", "answer": "ビビる、おじけづく"},
    {"question": "steal sb's/sth's thunder", "answer": "（注目を奪って）〜よりも目立つ"},
    {"question": "in the driver's seat", "answer": "優位に立った、支持する立場にいる"},
    {"question": "out of the ordinary", "answer": "普通じゃない"},
    {"question": "pep talk", "answer": "モチベの上がる言葉、激励の言葉"},
    {"question": "get the lay of the land", "answer": "どんな感じか見る、状況を把握する"},
    {"question": "barking up the wrong tree", "answer": "（方向性・考え方を）完全に間違っている"},
    {"question": "moving target", "answer": "動く的、変化し続けるもの"},
    {"question": "time is of the essence", "answer": "スピード・時間が重要"},

    {"question": "wear one's heart on one's sleeve", "answer": "感情を表に出す"},
    {"question": "highly strung", "answer": "ピリピリした"},
    {"question": "cost an arm and a leg", "answer": "（値段が）ものすごく高い"},
    {"question": "go (right) down to the wire", "answer": "最後の最後まで分からない"},
    {"question": "lose face", "answer": "メンツを失う、メンツが潰れる"},
    {"question": "get one's wires crossed", "answer": "勘違いする"},
    {"question": "up one's game", "answer": "もっと頑張る"},
    {"question": "catch-all", "answer": "（様々な種類を）すべて含める"},
    {"question": "shake sth up", "answer": "大きな変化をつける"},
    {"question": "knock on wood", "answer": "（幸運を願って）祈る、頼む"},
    {"question": "where there's a will, there's a way", "answer": "意思あるところに道は開ける"},
    {"question": "make sb's ears bleed", "answer": "(曲や音が）本当に嫌い"},
    {"question": "pull the wool over sb's eyes", "answer": "〜の目をごまかす、だます"},
    {"question": "put one's house in order", "answer": "自分のことをきちんとする"},
    {"question": "take sth/sb lightly", "answer": "〜を軽く考える、甘く見る"},
    {"question": "throw sb to the wolves", "answer": "〜を犠牲にする、見捨てる"},
    {"question": "food for thought", "answer": "考える材料、考える価値のあること"},
    {"question": "a picture is worth a thousand words", "answer": "図・写真の方がわかりやすい"},
    {"question": "taken care of", "answer": "済んだ、（問題が）なんとかなった"},
    {"question": "sneak out", "answer": "（こっそり）抜け出す"},

    {"question": "reach a tipping point", "answer": "転換期を迎える"},
    {"question": "see for yourself", "answer": "自分の目で確かめる"},
    {"question": "blow one's own horn", "answer": "自慢する"},
    {"question": "out of the woods", "answer": "危機を脱した"},
    {"question": "ups and downs", "answer": "浮き沈み"},
    {"question": "up-and-coming", "answer": "有望な、注目の"},
    {"question": "I'll cross that bridge when I get there", "answer": "その時になったら考えるよ"},
    {"question": "by the skin of one's teeth", "answer": "ギリギリで"},
    {"question": "oddball", "answer": "変なやつ、変わってる人"},
    {"question": "stick one's neck out", "answer": "危険を冒す、リスクを取る"},
    {"question": "scramble to get sth down", "answer": "慌てて〜をおわらせる"},
    {"question": "honeymoon period", "answer": "いい時期、人気のある時期"},
    {"question": "keep sb in line", "answer": "〜をコントロールする、行儀よくさせる"},
    {"question": "God only knows", "answer": "誰も分からない"},
    {"question": "refresher", "answer": "思い出させるもの"},
    {"question": "extend an olive branch", "answer": "仲直りしようと言う"},
    {"question": "count one's chickens before they hatch", "answer": "（結果が）確実だと思い込む"},
    {"question": "trickle in", "answer": "（人が）ボツボツ来る"},
    {"question": "raise the stakes", "answer": "重みを増す"},
    {"question": "no strings attached", "answer": "無条件、条件なし"},

    {"question": "bury one's head in the sand", "answer": "（現実から）目をそむける"},
    {"question": "double down", "answer": "強化する、力を入れる"},
    {"question": "take center stage", "answer": "注目を集める"},
    {"question": "fit for a king", "answer": "豪華な、贅沢な"},
    {"question": "Achilles heel", "answer": "弱点、弱み"},
    {"question": "play sth up", "answer": "〜を誇張する、（話を）盛る"},
    {"question": "slice and dice sth", "answer": "〜をとらえる、分析する"},
    {"question": "half-baked", "answer": "中途半端な、いい加減な"},
    {"question": "urban legend", "answer": "都市伝説"},
    {"question": "force sb's hand", "answer": "（意図に反して）〜をそうさせる"},
    {"question": "where there's smoke, there's fire", "answer": "火のない所に煙は立たぬ"},
    {"question": "smell a rat", "answer": "何か怪しいと思う"},
    {"question": "all good things must come to an end", "answer": "どんな良いことにも終わりがある"},
    {"question": "when all's said and done", "answer": "なんだかんだ、結局のところ"},
    {"question": "play the long game", "answer": "長期的な視点を持って行動する"},
    {"question": "devil's in the detail", "answer": "（簡単そうに見えて）実際は難しい、複雑な"},
    {"question": "hold all the cards", "answer": "極めて有利な状況にある"},
    {"question": "great minds think alike", "answer": "考えることが似ている"},
    {"question": "the good life", "answer": "良い暮らし"},
    {"question": "have sb on a leash", "answer": "〜を尻に敷く、支配する"}
]